棺材上
The coffin...
有你名字的缩写 J.B.
it has your initials, J.B.
那只是我们的共同点
At this moment, rather him than me.
至少你不必动手除掉他
At least you've been saved the effort of removing him.
听说布瓦上校在睡眠中过世的
Colonel Bouvar passed away in his sleep, so they tell me.
听你的口气 好像没亲手杀死他而很失望
You sound disappointed you did not kill him yourself.
没错 布瓦上校杀了我两名同仁
I am. Jacques Bouvar murdered two of my colleagues.
有没有别的事 我们法国工作站能帮上忙的?
Is there anything else our French station can do for Monsiuer Bond?
也许待会儿
Later, perhaps.
正如我所说 待会儿 走
As I said, later. Come on.
夫人
Madame...
我来向你致最深的哀悼
I've come to offer my sincere condolences.
我亲爱的布瓦上校
My dear Colonel Bouvar...
你不该自 己动手开车门
I don't think you should have opened that car door by yourself.
那个穿著不错的老傢伙 也应该有一个
No well-dressed man should be without one.
没错 非常实际
Yes, very practical.
上车
Get inside.
- 追来了 - 快!
- They're coming to get me. - Hurry!
《007系列之霹雳弹》
不准停车 !
Hey, no parking here!
抱歉 拉果先生
Pardon, Monsieur Largo.
国际兄弟会协助 无国籍人士
The International Brotherhood for the Assistance of Stateless Persons...
纯粹是博爱性质
is purely philanthropic.
我们对政治不感兴趣
We're not interested in politics...
只对恢复你的权利有兴趣
only in your rehabilitation.
我们已安排好巴西签证
We have been able to arrange for visas at the Brazilian Consulate.
兄弟会会照顾你们 直到…
The Brotherhood will look after you until...
- 早 拉果先生 - 早
- Good morning, Mr. Largo. - Good morning.
- 很高兴你再回来 - 谢谢
- Nice to have you back again. - Thank you, my dear.
- 我们会偿还一切 - 没有必要
- We pay back everything! - There will be no need.
我们有私人企业捐款
We have certain funds from private individuals who share our aim.
二号 坐下 我们等下讨论
Sit down, Number Two. We will discuss...
你的北约计划
your NATO project later.
我很遗憾通知大家 幽灵六号的死讯
I regret to inform you all of the death of Spectre Number Six.
布瓦上校遭到不知名刺客杀害
Colonel Jacques Bouvar was killed by an unknown assassin.
他的成就会被记住
His services will be greatly missed.
现在进行各地区财物报告 七号
We will now proceed with the area financial reports. Number Seven.
勒索双重间谍 马兹富吉瓦
Blackmail of the double agent Matsou Fujiwa.
不幸地 只有四千万日币
Unfortunately, only 40 million yen.
- 他只有这么多 - 十号
- All the man had. - Number Ten.
贝拉的暗杀案 那位法国反物质专家
Assassination of Perringe, the French antimatter specialist...
逃往俄国
who went over to the Russians.
从特别部门
Three million francs from the special department...
- 弄到三百万法郎 - 五号
- of the Quai D'Orsay. - Number Five.
我们在英国的火车劫案 二十五万英镑
Our consultation fee for the British train robbery: 250,000 pounds.
十一号
Number 11.
中共和美国贩毒份子的捐献
Distribution of Red China narcotics in the United States...
二百三十万元 由九号和我亲自去收的
2,300,000 dollars, collected by Number Nine and myself.
二百三十万…
Two million three...
我们的估计应该要高点 十一号
Our expectations were considerably higher, Number 11.
拉丁美洲的竞争 价格下跌
Competition from Latin America. Prices are down.
我已经预测到了
I anticipated that factor.
你确定所有的钱
Are you quite sure all monies...
都由你本人和九号清点过吗?
have been accounted for by yourself and Number Nine?
- 一号 每一分钱都点过 - 正好相反
- To the penny, Number One. - On the contrary...
我认为你们之中
I have satisfied myself that one of you is clearly...
有一人盗用公款
guilty of embezzlement.
魔鬼党要求党员们
Spectre is a dedicated fraternity...
绝对忠心
whose strength lies in the absolute integrity of its members.
我已知道罪犯是谁
The culprit is known to me.
我决定采取适当的行动
I have decided on the appropriate action.
现在进行新的方案
Let us now proceed with new business.
由负责北约计划的二号来讲解
We will hear from Number Two, who's in charge of our NATO project...
这是魔鬼党有史以来 最有野心的计划
the most ambitious Spectre has ever undertaken.
二号 你来报告
Your report, Number Two.
一号 谢谢
Thank you, Number One.
我们的目的 是要向北大西洋公约组织
Our intention is to demand a ransom...
要求赎金
from the North Atlantic Treaty Powers...
二亿八千万美金
of 280 million dollars...
一亿英镑
100 million pounds.
我已派力比男爵探员 到英国南部
I have sent Spectre agent Count Lippe to the south of England...
作必要的准备
where he is making the necessary preparations.
他在一家健身诊所
He is at a health clinic...
诊所座落在北约基地附近
conveniently located near the NATO air base.
- 派特? - 哈罗
- Oh, Pat? - Hello.
- 洗完澡 我再来找你 - 很快就好了
- I'll see you when I've had a shower. - I'll soon be finished.
- 邦德先生 力比男爵 - 你不会要带她走吧?
- Mr. Bond, Count Lippe. - You're not taking her away already?
她是这乏噪无味的地方 唯一的乐子
She's the only joy in this dreary place.
我看得出你也发现这点
I see you've discovered that too.
- 派特 再半小时 - 我会马上好
- About half an hour, Pat. - I'll be ready.
我听过这句话
I've heard that before.
邦德先生 幸会
Nice to have met you, Mr. Bond.
很怪的伤 跌倒的吗?
Funny looking bruise. A fall?
被一个寡妇拿火钳弄伤的
A poker in the hands of a widow.
我很意外 我以为你很对寡妇的口味
I'm surprised. I'd have thought you were just the type for a widow.
这位可不是 他完全不喜欢我
Not this one. He didn't like me at all.
红色方块 中间有个长钉穿过
A red square with a spike through it.
我认为是个秘密记号 澳门的红龙组织
I think it's a Tong sign, the red dragon from Macao.
- 要记录组帮我查证一下 - 甜心 抱歉 你在休假
- Ask records to verify it for me. - Sorry, sweetie. You're off duty.
- 你回来时 再通知你 - 钱班霓
- File it till you get back. - Moneypenny...
下次看到你 我会将你压在膝下
next time I see you, I'll put you across my knee.
外加果冻和柠檬汁? 我等不及了
On yogurt and lemon juice? I can hardly wait.
派特 快
Come on, Pat.
马上来
I'm coming.
我听不到你 你昏倒了吗?
I can't hear you. Have you fainted?
(力比爵士)
邦德先生 你迟到了
You're late, Mr. Bond.
我?
Me?
我真认不出我自 己了
I'd never have recognized myself.
- 我还好吗? - 可惜太健康了 请脱掉浴袍
- Do I seem healthy? - Too healthy. Take off your bathrobe.
你的口气好像不很坚持
You never say that as if you meant it.
手举过头
Arms above your head, please.
邦德先生 安分点 !
Behave yourself, Mr. Bond!
我看只有一个地方能让你安静
I can see there's only one place to keep you quiet.
这是什么?
What's this?
活动伸张椅 调整脊椎骨用的
A motorized traction table for stretching the spine.
有人称苦刑架
Some patients call it the rack.
这倒不意外
I'm not surprised.
上来吧
Get on.
踢踏板在哪?
Where's the kick starter?
别闹了 面向下
Stop fooling around and face down, please.
面向下
Face down.
力比男爵隔壁的人是谁?
By the way, who is the man in the room next to your Count Lippe?
我对他不太清楚
I really don't know too much about him.
安吉洛先生
A Mr. Angelo.
他跟私人医生一起来 疗治一场可怕车祸的伤
He's here with a private physician, recuperating from an awful car crash.
第一次我一整天 感觉真正安全
There, now, the first time I've felt really safe all day.
我15分钟后再来看你的情况
I'll look in and see how you're doing in 15 minutes.
幸会
Nice to have met you.
回来 !
Hey, come back!
救命 !
Help!
感谢老天 !
Oh, thank God!
你可能会被害死 !
You could've been killed!
我一定高了 6英寸
I must be six inches taller.
可怜的傢伙
You poor dear.
我想不出怎么会发生?
I can't think how it could have happened.
我可以告诉你 简直是奇迹 我会回来
I can tell you, it's a miracle I came back when I did.
我想你一定是无意间 碰到了开关
I can only think that you must have pushed the switch accidentally.
你最好跟我来
You better come along with me.
在蒸气室待一下 会帮助你放轻松
Spend a few minutes in the steam room. It'll help to relax you.
- 好 - 也许能帮你缩回去
- Yes. - Might even shrink you back to size.
有人希望今天的事没有发生
Somebody's going to wish today had never happened.
你不会告诉威医生吧
You wouldn't tell Dr. Wain.
求求你 我会丢饭碗
Please, I'd lose my job.
我想我沉默总有个代价
Well, I suppose my silence could have a price.
你不会是指…不
You don't mean... Oh, no.
是
Oh, yes.
待会见 鳄鱼
See you later, irrigator.
- 你在搞什么飞机? - 别担心 我会告诉大厨
- What the hell are you doing? - Don't you worry. I'll tell the chef.
放我出去 !
Let me out of this bloody machine!
救命 !
Help!
(热疗中心)
皮草
Mink.
可以消除紧张
It reduces the tensions.
对我不管用
Not mine.
杜瓦少校社交秘书
Major Derval's social secretary.
- 我找安吉洛先生 - 什么?
- I would like to speak to Mr. Angelo. - What's that?
- 安吉洛先生 - 抱歉
- Mr. Angelo. - I'm sorry.
你拨错了
You got the wrong number.
你想脱掉这个 会不会舒服些…
You don't think you could be more comfortable if you take off this...
- 什么事? - 杜瓦少校?
- Yes? - Major Derval?
- 是 我就是 - 你的车在等了
- This is Major Derval. - Your car is waiting.
谢谢 我马上下来
I'll be down right away. Thank you.
我的车来了 任务到了 我的生活故事
My car's here. Duty calls. The story of my life.
你到空军基地会迟到
You'll be late at the air base.
此外 你会有时间冷静
Besides, it will give you time to cool off.
我回来时 你还在此吗?
You'll be here when I come back?
到时候也许就没心情了
But I may not be in the mood then.
- 你要打赌吗? - 你很清楚
- Do you wanna bet? - You know your Francois.
我了解我自 己
I know me.
好
All right.
- 我说过会下去 - 先生 你的外套
- I told him I'd be down. - Your coat, sir.
降落愉快 !
Happy landing!
谢谢
Thank you.
要乖 至少到我回来
Be good, at least until I get back.
- 没人看见我们 走道没人 - 门关上 !
- Nobody saw us. The corridor's empty. - Shut the door!
他死了 力比 你掩护
He's dead all right. Lippe, you take over.
- 医生和救护车在外面吗? - 一切都如计划安排
- Are the doctor and ambulance outside? - Everything as arranged.
安吉洛
Angelo.
你的呼吸器具
Your breathing equipment.
隔离氧气系统
Isolates you from the oxygen supply.
伽马毒气 浓缩式 你刚用的那种 而最重要的…
Gamma gas. Instantaneous. Type you just used. And most important...
不够 十万元不够
Not enough. 100,000 dollars is not enough.
- 你想说什么? - 我改变主意
- What are you trying to say? - I changed my mind.
我花了两年
Two years of my life...
研究影片 报告
studying the film, the reports...
易容手术 模仿声音
plastic operations, voice lessons.
算是二十五万好了 要不你找别人
Make it a quarter of a million, or get someone else.
- 没有别人 - 没错 我是杜瓦
- There is no one else. - Exactly. I am Derval.
收起来 安吉洛说得没错
Put that away. Angelo is right.
我会通知一号 我们已重新安排过
I'll inform Number One we made a new arrangement.
这只是定金而已
This is merely a down payment.
好 但我要二十五万
All right, but against a quarter of a million.
- 同意 - 他的表
- Agreed. - His watch.
身分辨明卡
Identification Disc.
- 再见 ! - 不 他总说再会
- Au revoir! - No, he always says ciao.
帽子戴得太后面了
The cap's too far back on your head.
剩下的钱 准备好就好
The rest of my money, just have it ready.
来 帮他换上睡袍
Come on. Get him into his pajamas.
长官 麻烦证件
Sir, identity, please.
谢谢
Thank you, sir.
这是单机出击例行训练 你们将有一位
This is a normal training sortie, and you'll be accompanied...
北约代表同行 杜瓦少校
by a NATO representative, Commandant Derval...
北约杜瓦少校
Major Derval of NATO.
例行性飞行 驾驶猎犬式飞机
It's a routine flight. You'll be flying a Vulcan...
高度四万五千英尺
at an altitude of 45,000 feet...
携带二枚 M.O.S. 核弹
armed with two atomic bombs, M.O.S. Type.
雷管一样 在白色安全盒里
Fuses as usual in the white security box.
那些可恶的飞机 !
Oh, those damned aeroplanes!
够让你发疯的
They're enough to drive you mad.
除非是你那个皮草手套
Unless, of course, it's that mink glove of yours.
我去把噪音关掉
I'll shut out the noise.
詹姆斯 你要去哪儿?
James, where are you going?
哪儿都不去 我只想运动一下
Nowhere. I thought I'd take a little exercise.
你开什么玩笑
You must be joking.
来
Come on.
安静 !
Quiet!
我能效劳吗? 郡府警局
Can I help you? County Police here.
喂?
Hello?
- 怎么回事? - 不知道
- What's going on? - I don't know.
是大门口电铃吗?
Could it be the front doorbell?
- 绝对不是 - 那会是谁?
- It most certainly could not. - Hello.
你晚上运动得还不够吗?
Haven't you had enough exercise for one evening?
你会这么说真奇怪
It's funny you should say that.
回转时间
Point of return...
45分30秒
45 minutes, 30 seconds.
人工操作换成自动驾驶
Switch from manual to auto.
换成自动了 少校
It's set on automatic. Commandant...
你能和副驾驶换位子吗?
would you care to change places with the copilot?
- 这里视野比较好 - 我很乐意
- Better view up here. - I'd be delighted.
这里是南方雷达
This is Southern Radar.
你正在被雷达监视中
You are now under positive radar control.
这是不被允许的
This is avoiding action.
请说出方位
Request you report your position.
拿著 好吗? 什么事?
Take this, will you? What's the flap, Dawson?
O-B-N-R 长官 北约训练飞行 监控站告诉我们
O-B-N-R, sir. NATO training flight. Air traffic flashed us.
在雷达上消失 到处找不到
They lost it on radar. We haven't been able to pick it up anywhere.
它从荧幕上消失前 最后高度是多少 ?
Was she losing altitude when she went off the screen?
相当快 三百英尺以下我们搜不到
Rapidly. We can't scan below 300 feet.
- 也许坠机 - 她发生问题吗?
- She may have gone down. - Was she in trouble?
最后一次报告中没有 约在这里
Not according to the last report, which came from about here.
- 她携带武器对吗? - 两枚核子武器 M.O.S. 型
- She is armed, isn't she? - Two atomic weapons, M.O.S. Type.
派出所有的人 到附近区域地毯式搜索
Get everything you can into the area. A thorough search.
立刻通知总部 第一优先 绝对机密
Notify the Admiralty at once. Top priority. Absolute security.
- 同时联络华府 - 遵命 长官
- Ask them to contact Washington. - Very good, sir.
有看到别的东西吗?
Is there anything else in sight?
没有 一切没问题
No. All clear.
打开水下降落灯
Switch on the underwater landing lights.
打开水下舱门
Open the underwater hatch.
- 待命接潜水艇 - 绞盘 !
- Stand by to winch in the submarine. - Man the winches!
- 快把盒子拿给古先生 - 是
- Give these bomb fuses to Mr. Kutze. - Right, sir.
快把潜艇弄出来 把炸弹放进容器内
Get the submarine up quickly and the bombs loaded in the containers.
尤古 对你新玩具满意吗?
Kutze, are you pleased with your new toys?
一些新安全装置 秘密控制
Some new safety device. A secret control.
有什么是伟大的古斯 处理不了 ?
What can they have that the great Ladislav Kutze cannot handle?
在我实验室里 生活单纯多 了
Life was much simpler in my Warsaw laboratory.
你的那份相当于 几份的诺贝尔奖金?
Your share will amount to how many Nobel Prizes?
往前拉 !
Pull forward!
再来 停 !
More. Hold it!
从巴黎来的 一号在线上
Paris, sir. Number One on the scrambler.
我是二号 第二步完成
Number Two speaking. Phase two completed.
二号做的很好 不像力比爵士
Number Two has done well, unlike Count Lippe...
选择了安吉洛 差点危害到我们计划的成功
whose choice of Angelo might have jeopardized the success of our project.
传话到刺杀部
Send a message to the Execution Branch.
至少每天写信或打电话
You will write, or telephone at the least.
我真的很抱歉 如此急急忙忙的走
Day by day. I'm truly sorry I have to dash off like this.
但办公室有急事
There's been a bit of a flap at the office.
- 你从事哪方面行业? - 我到处旅游
- What kind of work do you do? - I travel...
类似处理疑难杂症的专家
sort of a licensed troubleshooter.
安吉洛先生 昨晚心脏病发
Mr. Angelo. Heart attack last night.
我不意外
I'm not surprised.
- 保持联络 - 詹姆斯 随时随地
- Keep in touch. - Anytime, James. Anyplace.
改天改地
Another time, another place.
- 你迟到了 ! - 对
- You are late! - Yes.
时下有些人开车 真的很令人火大
Some people on the road really burn you up these days.
在会议室 重大事件
In the conference room. Something pretty big.
欧洲每位0 0探员都到齐 还有内政大臣
Every Double-0 man in Europe has been rushed in, and the Home Secretary too.
他太太的狗可能走失了
His wife's probably lost her dog.
好 现在人都到齐了…
Well, now that we're all here...
首相要内政大臣
The Prime Minister has asked the Home Secretary...
代表他来此
to come and represent him here today.
内政大臣请
The Home Secretary.
各位 你们将要听到的录音带
Gentlemen, the tape that you are about to hear...
是今早十点收到的
was received at 10 Downing Street this morning.
亲爱的首相先生
My dear Prime Minister.
二枚核弹
Two atomic bombs...
四 五 六和四 五 七
numbers 4-5-6 and 4-5-7...
装载在北约7 5 9号飞机上
which were aboard NATO flight 7-5-9...
现在已归魔鬼党所有
are now in the possession of Spectre.
除非在往后七日 贵政府
Unless within the next seven days your government...
付给我们 一亿英镑
pays to us 100 million pounds sterling...
不然我们就会发射飞弹
in a manner to be designated by us...
炸毁 英国
we shall destroy a major city in England...
或美国重要城市
or the United States of America.
请在明天下午六点钟时
Please signal your acceptance of our terms by arranging...
将伦敦大钟敲响七下
for Big Ben to strike seven times...
表示接受我们的条件
at 6:00 p. m. Tomorrow.
首相和总统
The Prime Minister and the President...
已经透过电话商讨 并同意
have talked together over the hot line and have agreed...
除非找回炸弹 不然就得付款
that unless the bombs are recovered, payment will have to be made.
为了避免重大惊慌
To avoid general panic...
目前将仍列为机密
complete secrecy will be maintained and no press announcements.
首相要你们部门
The Prime Minister has asked that your department...
负责所有行动
take charge of the operation.
谢谢你 约翰爵士
Thank you. Sir John.
这记录表示猎犬式飞机 最大行程的范围
This circle represents the full flying range of the Vulcan.
全面搜查已找不到任何 失事或降落的证据
Extensive search has failed to locate any evidence of either a crash...
全世界的报告已证实
or landing, and worldwide reports have proved negative...
各机场也未有猎犬式飞机降落
on all airfields large enough to handle the Vulcan.
- 这是目前仅有的资料 - 约翰爵士 谢谢
- That's all we have, sir. - Thank you, Sir John.
我让你们继续接手这个案子 我们会以十号线保持联络
I'll leave you to carry on. We'll keep you in touch from Number 10.
谢谢 长官
Thank you, sir.
你们现在打开前面的卷宗
You may now open the folders in front of you.
代号: 霹雳弹
Code name: Thunderball.
你们也看得出来 资料不多
As you can see, we've very little to go on.
所有机员
All the members of the crew...
都经过最安全的检查
had top security clearance.
照片都在档案里
You'll find their photographs and service records in your files.
你们将和北约组织 中情局
You'll be working with NATO, C.I. A...
以及所有盟国情治单位一起合作
and all allied intelligence units.
就这样
That's all...
直到你们和我讨论个人任务
until you discuss your individual assignments with me.
我派你去加拿大
I've assigned you to station C, Canada.
克上尉会是你空军指导
Group Captain Pritchard here will be your Air Force liaison.
长官 我很慎重 建议你派我去拿索
Sir, I respectfully suggest that you change my assignment to Nassau.
除了你热衷水上运动外 还有别的理由吗?
Is there any other reason besides your enthusiasm of water sports?
也许是这个
Perhaps this, sir.
- 如何? - 有一张这个人的照片
- Well? - There was a photograph of that man...
在档案夹里
in this dossier you gave us.
他名叫杜瓦
His name is Derval.
我昨晚看到他 但他已经死了
I saw him last night at Shrublands, but he was dead.
不 不可能 他昨晚
Oh, no, sir. Not possible. He was seen...
还登上猎犬式飞机起飞
boarding the Vulcan and took off last night.
如果007他说昨晚 看见杜瓦死
If 007 says he saw Derval last night and he was dead...
我就不会再质问
that's enough for me to initiate inquiries.
当然
Yes, of course.
- 这女孩是谁? - 杜瓦的妹妹
- Who is this girl? - Derval's sister.
- 知道她现在在哪吗? - 拿索
- Do you know where she is now? - Nassau.
你认为有必要调查她吗?
Do you think she's worth going after?
我不会错过
I wouldn't put it quite that way.
只有四天
We've only got four days.
别花时间坐在这儿
Don't spend your time sitting around.
我不会 长官
No, sir, I won't.
祝你好运
Good luck.
长官 谢谢
Thank you, sir.
身材真好 我想
Smashing figure. I don't suppose...
这和你请求毫无关系吧?
that has anything to do with your request?
我是天生被人误会的人?
Was there ever a man more misunderstood?
你骗不过我的双眼
You can't pull the wool over my eyes.
你也许能骗老头子 但我很清楚 我能…
You may be able to con the old man, but I know better. I could...
我也一样 钱班霓小姐
So do I, Miss Moneypenny.
你不叫我老头子 我会感谢你
And I'll thank you not to refer to me as the old man.
我想我进来时有顶帽子
I think I had a hat when I came in.
你怎么认出她?
How else will you recognize her?
绝对错不了 她左大腿上有二个胎记
Couldn't miss. She has two moles on the left thigh.
- 谢谢你… - 詹姆斯邦德
- Thank you, Mr... - James Bond.
我在你下水后就来了
I arrived soon after you went down.
- 我很欣赏你的姿态 - 是吗?
- I've been admiring your form. - Have you?
你叫詹姆斯邦德 而很欣赏我的姿态
Your name's James Bond and you've been admiring my form.
大部分的女孩只是在玩水
Most girls just paddle around.
- 你游得跟男人一样 - 你也是
- You swim like a man. - So do you.
我常常练习
I've had quite a bit of practice.
- 你常来吗? - 无聊的时候就来
- Do you come here often? - Whenever I'm bored.
事实上 每天都来
Practically every day.
你还做些什么? 在哪做?
What else do you do, and where?
- 你从不浪费时间 是吗? - 是的
- You don't waste time, do you? - No.
- 当纪念 - 谢谢
- For effort. - Thank you.
我会穿戴起来 下次你就认得出我
I'll wear it so you know me next time.
我说得没错 绝对错不了
I was right. Couldn't miss.
- 我不明白 - 很快就会明白了
- I'm not with you. - You soon will be.
宝拉 !
Paula!
- 拉我一把 好吗? - 上来吧
- Give me a hand, will you? - Get in.
通知伦敦我联络上那个女孩
Tell London I've made contact with the girl.
我不认为那是"联络"
Well, it's not what I'd call contact.
我会说你看见她
I'll pass it through you've seen the girl.
- 继续加油 - 发动不了 !
- Keep trying. - It won't start!
我们马达坏了 !
Ahoy there! Our motor's conked out.
你不会要去珊瑚港附近吧?
You wouldn't be going anywhere near Coral Harbor, would you?
我本来不去 但可以绕一下
I wasn't, but I could.
我有个很重要的约会 会很感激你送我一程
I have a very important appointment. I'd appreciate a lift.
上来吧 !
Come aboard then!
你不介意搭别的船吧?
You don't mind taking the service boat, do you?
不会
Not at all.
快 !
Hurry up!
- 也许我们还能在泳池边午餐 - 你的紧急约会呢?
- Perhaps lunch by the pool. - How about your urgent appointment?
你来这里多久?
How long have you been out here?
约三周
About three weeks.
你一直都这么多问题吗?
Don't you ever stop asking questions?
好 改变战略 喝点我的海鲜汤
All right. Change of tack. Have some of my conch chowder.
邦德先生 你搞错了
You've been reading the wrong books, Mr. Bond.
- 海鲜汤吗? - 当一名调情圣手
- About conch chowder? - Being an aphrodisiac.
我正好喜欢海鲜汤
It just so happens that I like conch chowder.
你的朋友?
Friend of yours?
- 为我监护人工作 - 你的监护人监视你?
- Works for my guardian. - Your guardian has you watched?
- 他喜欢知道我在哪 - 我不怪他
- He likes to know where I am. - I don't blame him.
- 恕我失陪 - 你不会这么快就走吧?
- Will you excuse me? - You're not going so soon?
恐怕是如此
I'm afraid so.
我监护人的游艇
My guardian's yacht.
真的?
Oh, really?
- 他在等我 - 我能和你去吗?
- He'll be expecting me. - May I come with you?
- 想见见你的监护人 - 不行
- I'd love to meet your guardian. - Oh, no.
- 能再见到你吗? - 这岛很小
- Will I see you again? - It's a small island.
- 也许能一起吃晚餐 - 不行
- Perhaps we can have dinner together. - No.
- 真不合作的多明诺 - 你怎么知道?
- My dear, uncooperative Domino. - How do you know that?
你怎么知道我朋友 叫我多明诺?
How do you know my friends call me Domino?
你脚踝的链子上写的
It's on the bracelet on your ankle.
你眼睛真利
What sharp little eyes you've got.
等你尝到我的厉害之后
Wait till you get to my teeth.
再见 明天见
Bye then. See you tomorrow on the beach.
- 五百英镑 - 好的 先生
- 500 pounds, please. - Certainly, monsieur.
谢谢
Thanks.
抱歉
Sorry.
- 拿去 - 谢谢
- There. - Thank you.
二百
Two hundred.
八点
Eight.
总要有人输
Someone has to lose.
对 我以为你肩后有魔鬼
Yes, I thought I saw a spectre at your shoulder.
什么意思?
What do you mean?
失败的魔鬼 你要改运了
The spectre of defeat. Your luck was due to change.
我们很快就会知道
We'll soon find out.
提高赌注有异议吗? 五百英镑?
Any objection to raise the limit? 500 pounds shall we say?
- 太大了 - 我也退出
- Too big for me. - Count me out too.
也许你想接手
Perhaps you would like to take the shoe.
我朋友不会介意 先生是…
My friend won't mind, Mr...
- 邦德 - 是 邦德先生
- Bond. - Oh, yes. Mr. Bond.
- 我有位同事提过你 - 希望不是坏话
- One of my associates spoke about you. - Nothing bad, I hope.
是你的魔鬼跟我的对抗
It's your spectre against mine.
你希望我走厄运?
You wish to put the evil eye on me?
我来的地方有种对付的方法
We have a way to deal with that where I come from.
你也许会骗到我 看看对牌如何
You may hex me. Let's see what it does for the cards.
- 不要了 - 七点
- No. - Seven.
六点
Six.
八点
Eight.
九点
Nine.
邦德先生 你好像打不败
You seem to be unbeatable, Mr. Bond.
目前而已 这种事维持不久
For the moment. This sort of thing can't last.
艾米里欧 你答应请我一杯酒
Emilio, you promised to buy me a drink.
亲爱的 马上 我要先赢回来
Soon, my dear. I want to get my money back first.
能容我请小姐一杯酒吗?
May I be allowed to buy the lady a drink?
- 我会很感激 - 那我必须换手了
- I would appreciate that. - Then I must pass the shoe.
如果他不改手气 他会变得很无理
He's going to be impossible if his luck doesn't change.
我想今晚是不会变了
Somehow, I don't think it will tonight.
鱼子酱 房派里昂55年份的酒
Beluga caviar, Dom Perignon, '55.
- 先生 - 谢谢
- Monsieur. - Thank you.
我知道你是拉果先生的侄女
I understand you're Mr. Largo's niece.
要比情妇好听
Sounds better than... What would you say? Mistress? Kept woman?
我不会这么说 你在哪儿认识他的?
I wouldn't say that. Where did you meet him?
在凯菲勒 我跟我哥法兰克斯在那里
In Capri. I was there with my brother, Francois.
奇怪 我发现艾米里欧很有魅力
Strange. I found Emilio attractive...
之后?
then.
- 他住在船上吗? - 不 在岛上有房子
- Does he live aboard the yacht? - No. He has a house on the island.
- 一定要谈他吗? - 不
- Must we talk about him? - No.
- 我情愿跳舞 - 我也是
- I'd much rather dance. - So would I.
- 你哥现在在哪儿? - 英国
- Where is your brother now? - In England.
他是北约空军少校
He's a Commandant with the NATO forces there.
他人很棒
He's a wonderful person.
我却一直遇不到他那种人
The trouble is I never meet anyone like him.
- 只遇上拉果和我这种人 - 你不像拉果
- Only men like Largo and myself. - You are not like Largo.
不像吗?
No?
你为何这么说?
Why do you say that?
你抱我的方式
The way you hold me.
那边 !
There.
- 你在拿索待多久? - 后天离开
- How long are you staying in Nassau? - We're going the day after tomorrow.
我说过 我们时间不多
As I said, we haven't got much time.
艾米里欧想要离开
Emilio wants to leave.
你今晚睡在船上吗?
Are you sleeping aboard tonight?
我希望你别这么露骨
I hoped you'd not be so obvious.
当一个人时间不多 行动必须露骨
Well, when one has so little time, one sort of has to be obvious.
- 你知道哪儿能找到我 - 邦德先生
- You know where you can find me. - Mr. Bond.
你侄女是位好舞者
Your niece is an excellent dancer.
让我向你证明我是名好输家
Let me prove I'm as good a loser as you are a winner.
周日来吃中饭 我在波米拉的家
Come to lunch on Sunday. The Palmyra. It's my house.
那就决定在周日 中午
Sunday at noon, then.
亲爱的
My dear.
- 晚安 - 晚安
- Good night. - Good night.
你得逐字告诉我 邦德说的话
You must tell me what Mr. Bond had to say, word for word.
他谈起一些你的事
He talked about you a little.
他刚刚说了什么? 我没听清楚
What was he saying just then? I didn't quite hear.
他问今晚我们是否睡在船上
He asked were we sleeping aboard tonight.
有趣
Interesting.
- 我的钥匙 3 0 4房 - 3 0 4房 谢谢
- My key. It's 304, please. - Thank you. 304.
- 抱歉 没有信 - 谢谢
- I'm sorry, no mail. - Thank you.
哈罗 0 0…
Well, hello, 00...
这样对待中情局真不赖
That's a fine way to treat the C.I.A.
抱歉 菲立 但你正要说007
Sorry about that, Felix, but you were about to say 007.
拿著
Here.
你杀了他没?
Have you killed him?
你应该最了解我 去吧 笑面虎
You know me better than that. Here you go, Smiler.
看到你到此想看的吗?
Have you seen everything you came to see?
回你朋友那里去报告
Go back to your friends and report.
告诉他 小鱼我丢回海里给他
Tell them, the little fish I throw back into the sea. Give it to him.
你要从我背后开枪
You're going to shoot me in the back.
我是指枪
The gun, I mean.
快走 !
Get out!
- 他是谁? - 小鱼
- Who was he? - Like I said, a small fish...
替拉果先生工作
working for a Mr. Largo.
他有艘游艇 我们待会儿该去看看
He's got a yacht we should take a look at later.
- 要见拉果先生 - 让他进去
- Quist to see Mr. Largo. - Open up.
(波米拉 私人处所 非请莫入)
什么事? 是克利斯
Yes? It's Quist.
轻松点 朋友
Gently, my friend.
- 你查到什么? - 什么也没有
- What did you find? - Nothing.
- 你见到邦德了 ? - 见到了
- You saw Bond? - Yes, I saw him.
出 了什么事?
What happened?
你让他制服了你
You let him get the better of you.
嗨 你好 你终于联络上了吗?
Hey, there, did you finally make contact?
你迟到了 菲立 史莱德 我们在此的伙伴
You're late. Felix Leiter, this is Pinder, our man here.
- 幸会 - 各位 这边请
- How do you do? - This way, gentlemen.
- 那女孩是谁? - 宝拉 我这儿的助手
- Who's the girl? - Paula Kaplan, my assistant here.
他没有造访 美国的计划
He has no plans to visit the United States.
特别报导
Now here's a special announcement...
BB C外电
from the Overseas Service of the B.B.C.
大钟今晚六点时 确实敲了七下
Big Ben actually did strike seven times at 6:00 this evening.
是因为1895年的雷电
This was caused by a mechanical failure...
所造成的机械故障
which last occurred during a violent electrical storm in 1898.
让我们再度回到头条新闻
And here once again are the headlines.
显然是在拖延时间
Obviously stalling for time.
- 不 ! - 啊 007
- Oh, no! - Ah, 007.
- 真棒的惊喜 - 我也一样
- What a wonderful surprise. - For me too.
我得说 我觉得这些 你用来逃命的武器
I must say, I find this business of equipping you in the field...
他们是 非常的不寻常
on the run, as it were... highly irregular.
这是盖氏计算仪
Here we have a Geiger counter.
实用而不易损坏
Useful and unobtrusive.
这个短针会计算辐射能量
The sweep hand takes the radioactivity count.
- 当然也是防水的 - 当然
- It's waterproof, of course. - But of course.
我要你特别小心这个
Now, here's something I want you to use with special care.
- 特别小心 - 你所给我的一切…
- With special care. - Everything you give me...
我全都很小心使用 我知道
Is treated with equal contempt. Yes, I know.
但这是一具水底相机 按这个钮
But that's an underwater camera. It takes eight pictures...
就能连续拍八张照片
in rapid succession by pressing that button there.
- 这个设计很特别吗? - 如果你可以在黑暗中
- Is that clever? - If you can take pictures...
用红外线底片拍照 那就很特别
in the dark with an infrared film, yes.
试著别像往常滥用 007
Try to be a little less than your usual frivolous self, 007.
这是迷你信号弹
Here's a miniature Very pistol...
能发射很亮的红色信号
which fires a bright red flare, a distress signal.
你该全天候随身携带
You should keep it on you day and night.
我不喜欢你最后 说的那句话
I resent that remark.
你介意吗?
Look, do you mind?
当你在水下无法呼吸时
Now, in the event of a re-breather not being available...
你可以使用这个装置 当然只是短时间
you can use this device for short periods only, of course.
大约四分钟
Say, about four minutes.
- 聪明 - 不到最后关头别用
- Clever. - You'll only use it as a last resort.
很适合放在口袋里
It closes to a convenient pocket size.
假设有这样的口袋
Assuming one has a convenient pocket.
注意 最近发明的
Now pay attention. A recently developed...
无害无线电装置
harmless radioactive device.
无害的
Harmless.
自动发射至特殊接收器
It sends out a homing signal to a special receiver.
- 我该如何使用 ? - 很显然
- What am I supposed to do with this? - Obviously, you...
你得吞下去
swallow it.
现在?
Now?
希望她今晚还会停留在原地
Let's hope she'll still be lying in the same place tonight.
我们待会儿 可以用这双船身的船 当聚会的地方
We'll use this catamaran as a rendezvous place for later.
好主意
Good idea.
带她进来
Take her in.
有一个容器将会被投至 高棉海岸的
A container will be dropped off the coast of Burma...
满古群岛附近
in the Megui Archipelago...
落座于北纬2 0度 东经6 0度
latitude 20 degrees north, longitude 60 degrees east...
时间是在五月二十七日 格林威治时间下午八点
at 20 hundred hours Greenwich mean time on May 27.
里面有重3到8克拉不等的
It will hold blue-white flawless diamonds between...
无暇的蓝白钻石
three and eight carats.
总价值不准低于
Total value to be not less than 100 million pounds...
现在市价的一百亿英镑
present market price.
在我们收取容器
After we have recovered the container...
确认无误后
and verified its contents...
将以无线电频率 1 6点2 3兆赫
you will be notified on radio frequency 16.23 megacycles...
通知你们 何处可以找到核弹
where the atomic bombs may be recovered.
肯纳生 立刻去准备
Kenniston, you'd better get on to De Beers at once.
是
Yes, sir.
各位 除非找到炸弹
Well, gentlemen, unless those bombs are found...
我恐怕我们得付款
I'm very much afraid we'll have to pay their price.
- 长官 - 噢 对了
- Sir? - Oh, yes.
007拿索传来的电报
Signal from 007 in Nassau.
有一 、 二件事 会引起我们的兴趣
One or two things that might interest us.
迪斯可戈兰号仍在港口 停泊在赌场航线
The Disco Volante is still in the harbor, lying off the casino channel.
双船身的船也在 能利用它当掩护
The catamaran is there too, so we can use it for cover.
很好 你们可以在船后放我下水
That's fine. You can drop me in the water behind her.
- 伦敦有进一步的消息吗? - 没有
- Any further news from London? - No.
仍是2 7 日晚上八点
Zero hour is still 20 hundred hours on the 27th.
- 现在只剩5 5小时 - 我们走吧
- That's just 55 hours from now. - Yes. Shall we go?
- 这里可以了 - 我们在潘德那儿见
- Okay, this will do here. - We'll meet back at Pinder's.
祝你好运
Good luck.
打开水下灯
Turn the underwater lights on.
打开闭路电视 特写的 !
TV, closed-circuit!
手榴弹
Hand grenades.
准备好了
Ready.
这下面
Down there.
那边 !
There!
那边有东西 !
Hey, there's something there!
推进器一定撞到他了
Look! Must have hit him with the propeller.
让我们回去告诉拉果
Let's get back and tell Largo.
- 能载我一程吗? - 当然
- Can I have a lift? - Sure.
谢谢 你救了我一命
Thank you. You just about saved my life.
我的船翻了 我得游上岸
My outboard capsized, so I had to swim ashore.
你要到哪儿?
How far do you go?
最好系上安全带
You better fasten your safety belt.
你叫什么名字?
What's your name?
詹姆斯邦德
James Bond.
休娜戈比
Fiona Volpe.
- 你常来这儿吗? - 我让你紧张吗?
- Do you fly here often? - Do I make you nervous?
不 我只是不想一晚
No, it's just that I have no desire...
被困住二次
to be capsized twice in one night.
至少你不必游上岸
At least you won't have to swim ashore.
邦德先生 你以前来过这吗?
Have you been here before, Mr. Bond?
没有 但这是往拿索的路吧?
No, I haven't. But this is the road to Nassau?
是的 总会到的
Yes, eventually.
- 我就到这儿 - 我也是 这是我的旅社
- Well, this is as far as I go. - Me too. This is my hotel.
- 真巧 - 是 真方便
- What a coincidence. - Yes, so convenient.
你脸色很苍白 希望我没吓到你
You look pale. I hope I didn't frighten you.
我一向是位紧张的乘客
You see, I've always been a nervous passenger.
有些男人不喜欢被载
Some men just don't like to be driven.
不 有些男人只是 不想被载著兜风
No, some men just don't like to be taken for a ride.
看这个
Look at this.
水下舱门
An underwater hatch.
原来他们这样进出
Yeah. So that's how they could leave and get back.
对 又没人看见 很显然 整个行动
Yes, and nobody saw them. Obviously the whole operation...
都在水下进行
was carried out underwater.
所以那是我们要找飞机的地方 走
That's where we'll have to look for the plane. Come on.
等照片干了之后 我会送到旅社
I'll bring the prints to the hotel when they're dry.
别忘了 空军已经搜索了 拿索250英里内的周围
Don't forget the Air Force searched the area 250 miles out of Nassau.
一定在范围外
It must be beyond that radius.
那就是迪斯可戈兰号 那晚停的地方
That's if the Disco Volante was out that night.
当然 但海港管制员说 她只出去了六小时
Sure she was, but harbor control said for only six hours.
六小时内不可能航行五百英里
She couldn't cover 500 miles in that time, no.
在六小时内 她来回的里程顶多九十英里
About 90 miles is her limit for six hours, and that's out and back.
我建议我们往远一点走 那我们就需要加油了
I reckon we've got to go further out. We'll need more gas for that.
好 我们回拿索
All right. Let's get back to Nassau.
- 时间不多了 - 没错 时间是不多了
- We haven't got much time. - You're right, we haven't.
放!
Pull!
他们当然在监视我们
Of course they are watching us.
不然他们还能干嘛?
What else have they to do?
- 你希望邦德死掉吗? - 想不出更好的安排
- You would like Bond dead? - I can think of no better arrangement.
因为他想和你女人做爱?
Because he tries to make love to your woman?
因为他是邦德 魔鬼党的敌人 应该除掉
Because he is Bond, and as an enemy of Spectre, he should be killed.
放!
Mark!
如果你昨晚的性急 造成邦德死亡的话
If Bond had died last night as a result of your hastiness...
他的政府就会发现炸弹在这儿
his government would have known for certain that the bombs are here.
时机成熟时 他会被杀 放!
When the time is right, he will be killed. Pull!
我会杀了他
I shall kill him.
单独的池子 一定是为了养鲨鱼 靠近点
A separate pool. For sharks, no less. Move in.
保持航向
Hold on that line.
那儿的确是拉果的地方 我下个拜访的地点
That's Largo's place, all right. My next port of call.
- 拉果先生? - 是的
- Mr. Largo? - Yes, sir.
谢谢
Thank you.
- 我能帮忙吗? - 当然能 邦德先生
- Can I help? - Why, Mr. Bond.
- 当然可以 - 这听起来特别令人动心
- Of course you can. - That looks particularly inviting.
- 欢迎到波米拉 - 我的荣幸
- Welcome to Palmyra. - It's a pleasure.
只希望没有打扰到什么
I just hope I'm not interrupting anything.
- 什么意思? - 我以为你有别的访客
- What do you mean? - I thought you had another visitor.
这把枪好像较适合女孩子
That gun, it looks more fitting for a woman.
你对枪很有研究?
You know much about guns?
不 我懂点女人
No. I know a little about women.
亚米先生 亚哥先生 亚哥先生 亚米先生
Mr. Jenni, Mr. Vargas. Mr. Vargas, Mr. Jenni.
- 哪一位是哪一位? - 我想你那天晚上
- Which is which? - I thought you might have met...
应该见过亚哥先生
Mr. Vargas the other night.
- 是的 - 喝酒吗?
- Yes, I believe I did. - Drink, sir?
- 兰姆可林酒好吗? - 好
- Rum Collins? - Yes.
时间正好 对吧?
Just about that hour, isn't it?
给你的? 当然 !
For you? Of course!
亚哥不喝酒 不抽烟
Vargas does not drink, does not smoke...
不做爱
does not make love.
亚哥 你会做什么? 每个人都有自己的喜好
What do you do, Vargas? Every man has his passion.
我喜欢钓鱼
Mine is fishing.
你呢 邦德先生?
What is yours, Mr. Bond?
我不是你所谓有喜好的人
Well, I'm not what you'd call a passionate man.
我该换件衣服了
I think it's time I went to change.
让我带你参观一下
You must let me show you around.
- 很乐意 - 我想你会喜欢的
- I'd love that. - I thought you might.
放!
Pull!
- 还有什么比这更容易的? - 也许你能帮我放一个
- What could be easier? - Perhaps you would call one for me?
- 当然 放! - 看来十分困难
- Of course. Pull! - It seems terribly difficult.
并不难 对吧?
No, it isn't, is it?
我为不同的海洋水族馆 收集大型凶暴鱼类
I collect big game fish for various marine institutions.
十分出色的动物 !
Magnificent creatures!
非常迷人
Charming.
恶名昭彰的黄金鲨
The notorious Golden Grotto sharks.
最野蛮 最危险
The most savage, the most dangerous.
它们知道喂食的时间到了
They know when it's time for them to be fed.
- 那船是你的吗? - 是 我十分以它为荣
- That boat, is she yours? - Yes. I'm very proud of her.
跑多快? 1 5节?
What does she do, about 15 knots?
比那要好 接近20节
Better than that. Near 20.
- 也许你想去看看 - 是 很想看
- Perhaps you'd like to see over her? - Yes, I would very much.
- 午餐好了 - 亲爱的 谢谢
- Lunch is ready. - Thank you, my darling.
邦德先生 来吧 海鲜汤很香
Come along, Mr. Bond. The conch chowder smells delicious.
多明诺 我想
Domino, I was just thinking.
既然我今晚没空 也许邦德先生
As I'll be busy this evening, perhaps Mr. Bond will be kind enough...
能够带你去参加欢节庆 本地的嘉年华会
to take you to the Jankanoo, our local Mardi Gras.
你是我今晚的贵宾
You'll be my guest tonight.
- 非常谢谢你 - 是我的荣幸
- That's very kind of you. - It will be my pleasure.
邦德先生一定自视很高
Our Mr. Bond must have a very high opinion of himself.
自视很高?
Opinion?
他也和我约了
Yes. He has a date with me too.
失陪一下
Excuse me.
- 放开我 ! - 这边
- Let me go! - Over here.
别让她大声嚷嚷 用迷魂剂
Don't let her make so much noise. Use the chloroform.
拉果说过他会来 是吗?
Largo did promise he'd come, didn't he?
别担心 他会到
He'll be here. Don't worry.
我想那傢伙在向你打招呼
I think that man is waving at you.
下来这里
Come down here.
快 !
Quick!
失陪一下
Excuse me for a second.
- 詹姆斯 宝拉不见了 ! - 怎么会不见了 ?
- James, Paula's gone! - What do you mean, gone?
她已退房
She just checked out of the hotel.
你看好多明诺
You look after Domino. Watch her.
- 你想她查到什么了吗? - 不知道 但我会查明
- Do you think she was onto something? - I don't know, but I gotta find out.
- 你看好她 - 好
- You watch out for her. - Right.
好 谢谢
All right. Thank you.
总督不太开心 但已照你的要求
The governor's not very happy, but you'll have...
全岛实施停电
a power cut as requested all over the island.
我才不管岛上其他的地方
I don't give a damn about the rest of the island.
- 我只要波米拉停电 - 没问题
- I want the lights out in Palmyra. - You'll have it.
什么意思 她不肯招?
What do you mean, she won't talk?
别担心 她会招的
Don't worry, she will.
怎么了 ?
What's wrong?
- 停电了吗? - 对 全岛都停电了
- Is it a power failure? - Yes, all over the island.
打开紧急发电机
Switch over to the emergency generator.
拉果告诉过你要小心
Largo told you to be careful.
我没杀她 她一定是吞了毒药
I didn't kill her. She must have taken some poison.
藏在嘴里 是不是氰化物?
A capsule in the mouth. What do you think, cyanide?
她死了
She's dead.
是警卫 有人打昏他!
Ricardo, someone's got him!
搜索那边 你 到鲨鱼池!
Search that way! And you, the shark pool!
- 怎么回事? - 不知道
- What happened? - I don't know.
别管他! 这边!
Leave him! This way!
停!
Stop it!
傻瓜! 他让你们对彼此开枪!
You fools! He's got you all shooting at each other!
这边!
Over here!
不 我有更好的主意
No! I've got a better idea.
打开水闸 让它们吃
Lift the tunnel hatch and let them eat.
是
Yes, sir.
抱歉 希望你下次好运点
Sorry, old chap. Better luck next time.
告诉莱特看紧那个女孩 我会马上回去找他
Tell Leiter to stay with the girl. I'll get back to him as soon as I can.
- 还有事吗? - 告诉他宝拉死了
- Anything else? - Tell him Paula's dead.
你是不是走错房间?
Aren't you in the wrong room?
我站的地方可没错
Not from where I'm standing.
既然你来了 能不能给我穿些什么?
Since you're here, would you mind giving me something to put on?
总之 很高兴再见到你
Anyway, I'm very glad to see you again.
我很也高兴再见到你
I'm glad to see you again.
我感觉你在躲我
I had the feeling you've been avoiding me.
我不知道我们是隔壁邻居
I had no idea that we were next-door neighbors.
他们今天下午 才替我换房间
They just moved me down this afternoon.
很不寻常是吧? 似乎是…
It's extraordinary, isn't it? Almost as if...
故意的
As if it was intended.
是的 很不寻常
Yes, it is extraordinary.
你不要脱下湿衣服吗?
Shouldn't you get out of those wet clothes?
你会因感冒致死
You'll catch your death of cold.
你知道 我们快要迟到了
Look, you know we're going to be too late.
- 迟到什么? - 欢节庆
- Too late for what? - The Jankanoo.
我答应我朋友在那碰面
I promised my friends I'd meet them there.
也许你认识他 拉果
Perhaps you know them, the Largos.
问题 为何这么多问题
Questions. All I get is questions.
反正节庆会进行一整晚
But the music is gonna go on all night anyhow.
足以让你好好狂野一下 你喜欢狂野吗?
Enough to drive you wild. Do you like wild things?
狂野 你该被关进笼子里
Wild. You should be locked up in a cage.
这张床有如笼子的感觉
This bed feels like a cage.
这些铜条
All these bars.
你认为我在这里安全吗?
Do you think I'll be safe?
你把我的头发搞的乱七八糟 你这个性变态狂
You made a shocking mess out of my hair, you sadistic brute.
替我拉上拉链好吗?
Will you zip me up, please?
难怪你衣服穿的这么快
No wonder you can get dressed so quickly.
路上 我们还可以聊聊
On the way, we can have a little talk.
你会很有兴趣的 走
You may find it interesting. Come on.
我来了
I'm coming.
我不想错过什么
I hate to think I'm gonna miss anything.
现在我们可以找个地方 好好聊聊了
And now we can go somewhere for an interesting talk.
这绝对是你的朋友 请进
Friends of yours, no doubt. Come in.
你穿衣服也很快 我从镜子里没看到枪
You dress quickly too. I didn't see that gun in the mirror.
那无关紧要 但它一直都在枕头底下
Not that it matters, but that was under the pillow all the time.
你什么时候发现的?
When did you find out?
你戴的戒指跟拉果戴的一样
You're wearing the same ring as Largo.
- 是我喜欢戴的戒指 - 它本身有它的危险性
- It's a ring I like to wear. - Then it has its dangers.
是虚荣 邦德先生
Vanity, Mr. Bond.
- 那是一个你很了解的事 - 小姐
- It's something you know so much about. - My dear girl.
别往自 己脸上贴金 我今晚所做的是为国王和国家
Don't flatter yourself. What I did this evening was for King and Country.
你认为它带给我的是愉快吗?
You don't think it gave me any pleasure, do you?
当然 我忘了你的尊严
But of course. I forgot your ego.
邦德 只要他和女人做爱
James Bond, who only has to make love to a woman...
她就会听到天籁之音
and she starts to hear heavenly choirs singing.
她懊悔 而且立刻变得正派而纯洁
She repents and immediately returns to the side of right and virtue.
但不是这个女人
But not this one.
你竟会失败 一定是个打击
What a blow it must have been, you having a failure.
不能每次都赢
Well, you can't win them all.
由大厅带他出去 去开车
We'll take him out the front way. Go and get the car.
邦德先生 小心
Careful, Mr. Bond.
现在又要怎样?
Now what?
通知波米拉 告诉他们 我们被欢节庆游行挡住了
Get through to Palmyra and tell them we've been held up by the Jankanoo.
- 要喝酒吗? - 赶他走!
- Like to have a drink, man? - Get him away!
- 你别轻举妄动 - 滚开 !
- Don't you try anything now. - Get out of here!
- 真的烈酒 - 滚开 !
- It's real firewater. - Get out of here!
追他! 抓住他!
After him! Get him!
见到什么吗?
You haven't seen anything?
看 !
Look!
跟踪他 你走这边 你那边
Follow him. You that side, you there.
跟著我们
Stay with us.
(亲亲俱乐部)
- 谢谢 我非常乐意 - 乐意什么?
- Thank you, I'd love to. - Love to what?
- 你疯了 你知道吗? - 对 大傢伙不都这样?
- You're mad. Do you know that? - Yes. Isn't everyone?
我能介入吗?
May I cut in?
你该告诉我 你太太也在这里
You should have told me your wife was here.
你常来吗?
Do you come here often?
你逃不掉的
It's no good trying to escape.
我不想逃
I don't want to escape.
真的很奇怪 我已经习惯你的脸了
Strange as it may seem, I've grown accustomed to your face.
你何不安安静静的 跟我们走?
Why don't you come with us quietly?
你好像不太了解 我很享受这个时刻
You don't seem to understand. You see, I enjoy my dancing.
不介意我朋友坐一下吗? 她刚刚死
Do you mind if my friend sits this one out? She's just dead.
你们在早上六点离开 停在雅典加油
You'll leave here at 0600 hours and land at Aden to refuel.
然后到满古群岛空投
You will then proceed to the Megui Archipelago...
一定要瞄准在
to make your drop precisely at...
北纬20度 东经6 0度
20 degrees north, 60 degrees east.
钻石将装在 特殊的容器内
The diamonds will be in a special container.
我不喜欢像这样的让步
I hate to give in like this.
付了一大笔钱 还让他这样要挟我们
Paying the blood money, letting them beat us.
- 有别的选择吗? - 恐怕没有
- Have you an alternative suggestion? - I'm afraid I haven't.
你的手下 007 我以为他会调查出什么端倪
Your man, 007, I thought he was on to something.
- 我也这么认为 - 假警报?
- I thought so too, sir. - False alarm?
- 恐怕是 - 很显然
- I'm afraid so. - He obviously has...
容我这么说 他极具戏剧性
a highly developed sense of, shall we say, drama?
如果007认为他查到什么
If 007 thought he was on to something...
很可惜 他在开始前 没查清楚
It's a great pity he didn't make sure before he started to shout the odds.
我们还剩下1 4小时5 0分
Well, we have exactly 14 hours and 50 minutes.
然后我们就得付款 而且要装出笑脸 对吧?
Then I suppose we shall have to pay up and look as happy as we can. Shan't we?
就是这样了 詹姆斯 几乎全找过了
Well, that's it, James. We've looked about everywhere.
我们一定要找到那飞机
We've got to find that plane.
下面找不到 那是黄金礁
You won't find it down there. That's the Golden Grotto.
- 黄金礁? - 是的
- Golden Grotto? - Yeah. All you'll find...
那里只有鲨鱼
down there are sharks.
降低点 我要靠近点看
Take her down. I want a closer look.
- 看什么? - 别管 ! 快降低点 !
- At what? - Never mind! Take her down, quick!
降低点 我想我们找到了
Set her down. I think we've found it.
下面有反光 我去看看
There's something camouflaged down there. I'll take a look.
射其中一条鲨鱼 让其他鲨鱼忙一阵子
Shoot one of those sharks. It'll keep the others occupied.
不知道多久他们会吃光它
I don't know how long the others will take before they finish him off...
- 但他们会回来 - 我会注意
- but they'll be back. - I'll keep an eye on them.
很好
Good.
- 它在下面 - 炸弹在船上吗?
- She's down there, all right. - Are the bombs on board?
- 不在 - 真要命 下一步怎么做?
- No. - Great. What's our next move?
我们去查迪斯可戈兰号
就算炸弹不在船上 也马上就会到
If the bombs aren't aboard her now, they soon will be.
你要问谁 拉果吗?
Who are you going to ask, Largo?
没有必要
No, I don't think we'll have to.
我希望我们没吓到鱼
I hope we didn't frighten the fish.
海胆的刺 有毒
Ow! Sea egg spines. They're poisonous!
手给我
Here, give me your arm.
坐下
Sit down.
转身
Now turn over.
会有点痛
This is going to hurt a bit.
我第一次尝女人的味道 还不错
It's the first time I've tasted women. They're rather good.
你是唯一让我哭的男人
You're the only man to ever make me cry.
除了我哥以外 我们小时候
Except perhaps Francois, my brother, when we were children.
多明诺 我得告诉你一件事
Domino, I have to tell you something.
抱歉 詹姆斯 我不是故意要 谈起爱让你难堪
I'm sorry, James. I didn't mean to embarrass you, speaking of love.
- 我必须再次伤害你 - 你要离开了吗?
- I must hurt you again. - You're going away?
甜心 抱歉 都结束了
So sorry, my dear, but it's all over.
不 是有关你哥的事
No, it's about your brother.
他怎么了 ?
What about him?
他死了
He's dead.
发生什么事?
What happened?
说来话长 这跟你朋友拉果有关
It's a long story, and it involves your friend Largo.
我需要你帮忙
I need your help.
当然
Of course.
你是为此才和我做爱
That's why you made love to me.
我无法解释这是怎么回事
Look, I can't explain what this is all about.
- 但你一定要相信我 - 因为你要我帮你?
- But you must trust me. - Because you want me to help you?
拉果派人谋杀你哥 或是他下的命令
Largo had your brother murdered, or it was on his orders.
如果你不帮我
Hundreds of thousands of people will die very soon...
数以千计的人马上会死
if you don't help me.
那是我们所知道的 还有我们不知道的事
That much we do know, but there's something we don't...
炸弹 几时会 运到迪斯可戈兰号上?
The bombs, when they're being loaded aboard the Disco Volante.
- 我怎么才会知道? - 你必须查明
- How could I know that? - That you'll have to find out.
这不容易 可能会很危险
It won't be easy. It could be very dangerous.
他还能对我做什么事?
What can he do to me he hasn't already done?
你肯做吗?
Then you'll do it?
- 是的 - 很好
- Yes. - Good.
这是盖氏计算仪 你按这个
This is a Geiger counter. You press this lever.
如果开始有响声 表示核弹已经在船上
If it starts clicking, it means the bombs are aboard.
- 那时我该怎么办? - 到甲板上去
- What do I do then? - Go straight up on deck.
当迪斯可戈兰号被监视时 你会被发现
As the Disco Volante is being watched, you'll be spotted.
亚哥在你后面
Vargas, behind you.
真的?
Really?
他一定跟踪我们
He must have followed us.
我想他懂意思了
I think he got the point.
应该是拉果
It should have been Largo.
拉果? 他期望你什么时候回去?
Largo? When did he expect you back?
很快了 他说别太晚 他对这点非常坚持
Very soon now. He said not to be late. He was most insistent.
你最好直接回去 我来料理亚哥
You better go straight back. I'll take care of Vargas and everything here.
我是为了我哥这么做的 为了他对他做的事
Understand I'm doing this for my brother, for what he did to him.
不论发生什么事 答应我杀了拉果
But promise you will kill Largo for me, whatever happens.
- 时间不多了 - 好
- We haven't much time. - All right.
我想起一件事 也许不重要
Oh, something I remembered. It may not be important.
- 告诉我 每件事都很重要 - 运河上有条小桥
- Tell me. Everything's important. - There's a small bridge over the canal.
拉果绝不准陌生人靠近
Largo never allows strangers to go near it.
运河旁有一列台阶
By the canal there's a flight of steps.
- 通向哪儿? - 海底
- Where do they lead to? - Down into the sea...
波米拉寓所的远方
on the far side of Palmyra.
也许还是很重要
Perhaps it is important after all.
穿上装备
Put on your equipment.
是否收到女孩登上 迪斯可戈兰号的讯息?
Did we get a message saying the girl went on board the Disco?
是的 讯号已经收到
Yes, sir. Signal received at...
- 如果她已上船 007又在哪? - 这是个问题
- If she is on board, where is 007 now? - That's the question.
准备出发 倒数五秒
Stand by. Five seconds.
注意我的讯号
Watch my signal.
- 准备出发 - 遵命 船长
- Prepare to get underway. - Aye, aye, sir.
船长 起锚
Captain, weigh anchor.
立刻出发
Get underway immediately.
一旦取了货品 就前往目标区 迈阿密
Once we pick up the merchandise, head for our target area, Miami.
迪斯可戈兰号出发了
The Disco Volante's leaving, sir.
- 我告诉过你待在舱房里 - 里面很闷
- I told you to stay in your cabin. - It's stuffy in there.
- 我要透透空气 - 你没听见吗?
- I want a breath of air. - My dear, did you not hear me?
- 那个哪来的? - 今早买的
- Where did you get that? - I bought it this morning.
- 让我看 - 不要 为什么要让你看?
- Let me see. - No. Why should I?
我猜是邦德先生给你的吧 而且亚哥已经死了
Mr. Bond gave you this little toy, I imagine, and Vargas is dead.
甜心 你已经无路可逃
No, my dear. There is no escape for you.
像你的朋友 你有点太聪明了
Like your friend, you've been a little too clever.
现在你被逮到 !
And now you are caught!
多明诺 你给了我很多快乐
You have given me much pleasure, Domino.
除非你告诉我 邦德知道多少
But in return, unless you tell me how much Bond knows...
不然我就被迫 回报你极大的痛苦
I'll be forced to cause you great pain.
这代表热 这代表冷
This for heat, these for cold.
很科学化 很缓慢
Applied scientifically and slowly.
非常非常的慢
Very, very slowly.
- 你要什么? - 我们启动炸弹了
- What do you want? - We're activating the bombs.
- 你说你想知道 - 是的
- You said you wanted to be told. - Oh, yes.
小姐和我之间的私事
A private little matter between the young woman and myself.
走!
Go!
亲爱的 别指望了 没人来救你
Do not live in hope, my dear. There is no one to rescue you.
继续 !
Now go on!
幸好他吞下的
It's a good thing the homing capsule he swallowed...
自动发报器仍管用
is still working.
直直前进
Straight ahead.
向右
Go right.
找到他了 !
That's him!
停!
Hold it!
往上
Up.
用无线电通知 奥兰多海滩
Get your radio man on to Orlando Beach.
警告他们 目标是迈阿密
Warn them the target is Miami.
同时炸弹由迪斯可戈兰号
Also, the bomb is transferred from the Disco Volante...
转换到富列点
onto a wreck off Fowley Point.
对 抓住这个
Right. Hang on to that.
希望还沉得下去
And the kitchen sink.
一切看来很好
On you, everything looks good.
拿著
Take this.
祝好运
Good luck.
- 起锚! - 是
- Weigh anchor! - Aye, aye, sir.
- 放烟雾 - 现在
- Make smoke. - Making smoke now.
(迪斯可戈兰号 巴拿马)
- 准备分隔 - 待命
- Stand by for conversion. - Standing by.
分隔
Jettison cocoon.
分隔完成
Cocoon's away.
继续开火! 他们接近了 !
Keep firing! They're closing!
加强火力 !
Fire more, more!
等等 !
Wait a minute.
我们仍有一枚炸弹在船上
We've still got one bomb aboard.
他发疯了 ! 请帮我跟他们说
He's gone mad! Please talk to them for me.
告诉他们我只是做我该做的 我只是奉命行事
Tell them that I only did what I had to do, what I was told to do.
- 他在哪儿? - 炸弹现在不能引爆
- Where is he? - The bomb cannot be exploded now.
我把引爆器丢进海里
I threw the arming device into the sea.
- 明白吗? - 是
- Do you understand? - Yes.
抓住他!
Get him!
- 我很高兴我杀死他了 - 你很高兴?
- I'm glad I killed him. - You're glad?
- 他是谁? - 不知道 但他帮了我
- Who's he? - I don't know, but he helped me.
- 小心 ! 礁石 ! - 要触礁了 !
- Look out! The rocks! - The reef!
控制器卡住了 ! 走!
He's jammed the controls! Come on!
- 快跳! - 我不会游泳!
- Come on, now, jump! - I never learned to swim!
现在学还不迟
Never too late to learn.
潜下去 !
Get down!